Register of the Norwood F. Allman papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1943-1987
  - Balfour, Guthrie (Folder 45)
  - Baltze, Erich (Folder 46)
  - Bang How (Folder 47)
  - Barbeau, Mr. (Folder 48)
  - Baretto, Mr. (Folder 49)
  - Barry, Kevin (Folder 50)
  - Barth, Allan (Folder 51)
  - Barton, Shirley (Folder 52)
  - Bate, Arthur D. (Folder 53)
  - Baty, Thomas (Folder 54)
  - Baumler, Lt. (Folder 55)
  - Baxter, William J. (Folder 56)
  - Beaulieux, Amedee (Folder 57)
  - Becker, E. H. (Folder 58)
  - Bellstedt, Kapitan (Folder 59)
  - Belser, Howard J. (Folder 60)
  - Benedict, Ruth, "Selection of Personnel in China,", 1943 (Folder 61)
  - Bennett, Roy (Folder 62)
  - Bentz, Winifred (Folder 63)
  - Bercovitz, Nathaniel (Folder 64)
  - Bernard, Elizabeth (Folder 65)
  - Berrier, Hilaire du (Folder 66)
  - Betz, R. H. (Folder 67)
  - Bhamo, Dr. (Folder 68)
  - Bielfeld, L. A. (Folder 69)
  - Bieltchenko, A. T. (Folder 70)
  - Bird, H. J. (Folder 71)
  - Bisson, Thomas A. (Folder 72)
  - Bloomfield, Thomas (Folder 73)
  - Blunden, Edmund (Folder 74)
  - Boehringer, Carl (Folder 75)
  - Boerter, August (Folder 76)
  - Boladeras, Maria (Folder 77)
  - Boltze, Junerich (Folder 78)
  - Boothe, Clare (Folder 79)
  - Borchers, Hans (Folder 80)
  - Bordwell, P. H. (Folder 81)
  - Boribhandh, Phra (Folder 82)
  - Botsford, Constantine and Gardner (Folder 83)
  - Boyd, Ralph S. (Folder 84)
  - Boyd-Orr, Lord (Folder 85)
  - Bradshaw, Homer (Folder 86)
  - Brand, Kenny (Folder 86A)
  - Brandao, Mario (Folder 87)
  - Brayshay, J. E. (Folder 88)
  - Brewer Weeks Co. (Folder 89)
  - Brines, Russell (Folder 90)
  - Brister, Mr. (Folder 91)
  - Brodillini, Jina (Folder 92)
  - Bruce, David (Folder 93)
  - Bruce, General (Folder 94)
  - Bruce, George C. (Folder 95)
  - Burtt, Lucy (Folder 96)
  - Burma Central Administration (Folder 97)
  - Butler, Thomas (Folder 98)
  - Bryan, Robert T. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Budenz, Louis F. (Folder 2)
  - Bunting, Earl (Folder 3)
  - Buol, Lawrence (Folder 4)
  - Burhan (Folder 5)
  - Byfield, Robert S., "Vishinsky vs. American Business: Economic Booby Traps Used As Weapons Against the Free World,", n.d. (Folder 6)
  - Cadwallader, Fred (Folder 7)
  - Cairns, Alexander (Folder 8)
  - Calder, A. B. (Folder 9)
  - Calder-Marshall, R. (Folder 10)
  - Calhoun, A. D. (Folder 11)
  - California Texas Oil Company (Caltex) (Folder 12)
  - Caples Company (Folder 13)
  - Carey, H. Sterling (Folder 14)
  - Carroll, Earl (Folder 15)
  - Carlson, Evans F. (Folder 16)
  - Carpenter, J. Henry (Folder 17)
  - Carpenter-Alting, Captain (Folder 18)
  - Carter, Boake (Folder 19)
  - Carter, Edward C. (Folder 20)
  - Castro, Fidel (Folder 21)
  - CC Clique (Folder 22)
  - Cecil, Robert (Folder 23)
  - Cha, Ko-erh (Folder 24)
  - Chai, Hsiao-wu (Folder 25)
  - Chainam, Direk (Folder 26)
  - Chan, George (Folder 27)
  - Chan, Kai-kong (Folder 28)
  - Chan, R. (Folder 29)
  - Chan, U. K. (Folder 30)
  - Chan, Yam-hung (Folder 31)
  - Chang, C. C. (Folder 32)
  - Chang, Chang-lao (Folder 33)
  - Chang, Ch'ing-yu (Folder 34)
  - Chang, Chao-li (Folder 35)
  - Chang, Che (Folder 36)
  - Chang, Cheng-kun (Folder 37)
  - Chang, Chen-Yu (Folder 38)
  - Chang, Chi (Folder 39)
  - Chang, Chia-ao (Folder 40)
  - Chang, Chia Hutuktu (Folder 41)
  - Chang, Chia-shen (Folder 42)
  - Chang, Chien (Folder 43)
  - Chang, Chien-fei (Folder 44)
  - Chang, Chih-chiang (Folder 45)
  - Chang, Chih-chung (Folder 46)
  - Chang, Chih-pen (Folder 47)
  - Chang, Chih-ying (Folder 48)
  - Chang, Ching-chiang (Folder 49)
  - Chang, Ching-hui (Folder 50)
  - Chang, Ching-shan (Folder 51)
  - Chang, Chun (Folder 52)
  - Chang, Chun-li (Folder 53)
  - Chang, Chun-mai (Chang, Carson) (Folder 54)
  - Chang, En-to (Folder 55)
  - Chang, Erk-kang (Folder 56)
  - Chang, Fa-fei (Folder 57)
  - Chang, Fa-kuei (Folder 58)
  - Chang, Fa-kwei (Folder 59)
  - Chang, Fang (Folder 60)
  - Chang, Feng-yuan (Folder 61)
  - Chang, Fred (Folder 62)
  - Chang, H. H. (Folder 63)
  - Chang, Hon (Folder 64)
  - Chang, Hsiao-I (Folder 65)
  - Chang, Hsi-jou (Folder 66)
  - Chang, Hsin-hai (Folder 67)
  - Chang, Hsin-pei (Folder 68)
  - Chang, Hsueh (Folder 69)
  - Chang, Hsueh-liang (Folder 70)
  - Chang, Hsun (Folder 71)
  - Chang, Hua-fu (Folder 72)
  - Chang, Huan-hsiang (Folder 73)
  - Chang, Hui-ming (Folder 74)
  - Chang, Jen-chieh (Folder 75)
  - Chang, Jen-li (Folder 76)
  - Chang, John M. (Folder 77)
  - Chang, Jui-kuei (Folder 78)
  - Chang, Keng-nien (Folder 79)
  - Chang, K. N. (Folder 80)
  - Chang, Kia Ngau (Folder 81)
  - Chang, Kuo-cheng (Folder 82)
  - Chang, Kuo-shuen (Folder 83)
  - Chang, Kuo-tao (Folder 84)
  - Chang, Lan (Folder 85)
  - Chang, Li-sheng (Folder 86)
  - Chang, Mei-yun (Folder 87)
  - Chang, Ming-jiunn (Folder 88)
  - Chang, Nai-chi (Folder 89)
  - Chang, Pai-chuan (Folder 90)
  - Chang, Peng-chun (Folder 91)
  - Chang, Ping-chun (Folder 92)
  - Chang, Po-ling (Folder 93)
  - Chang, S. T. (Folder 94)
  - Chang, Sa (Folder 95)
  - Chang, Shih-chao (Folder 96)
  - Chang, Shu-han (Folder 97)
  - Chang, Su-min (Folder 98)
  - Chang, T. K. (Folder 99)
  - Chang, Ta (Folder 100)
  - Chang, Tai (Folder 101)
  - Chang, Tao-fan (Folder 102)
  - Chang, Tao-hsing (Folder 103)
  - Chang, Ten-jen (Folder 104)
  - Chang, Ting-cheng (Folder 105)
  - Chang, Ting-fan (Folder 106)
  - Chang, Tso-hsiang (Folder 107)
  - Chang, Tsung-chang (Folder 108)
  - Chang, Tung-shen (Folder 109)
  - Chang, Tung-su (Folder 110)
  - Chang, Tzu-chung (Folder 111)
  - Chang, Tzu-yi (Folder 112)
  - Chang, Wan-lu (Folder 113)
  - Chang, Wei-fan (Folder 114)
  - Chang, Wei-hsiang (Folder 115)
  - Chang, Wei-lan (Folder 116)
  - Chang, Y. M. (Folder 117)
  - Chang, Ya-tung (Folder 118)
  - Chang, Yen-ching (Folder 119)
  - Chang, Yen-tien (Folder 120)
  - Chang, Yi-chu (Folder 121)
  - Chang, Yi-kun (Folder 122)
  - Chang, Ying (Folder 123)
  - Chang, Yuan-jung (Folder 124)
  - Chang, Yuan-shan (Folder 125)
  - Chang, Yu-ching (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Chang, Yu-chuan (Folder 2)
  - Changchia (Folder 3)
  - Chao, Chen (Folder 4)
  - Chao, Cheng-ping (Folder 5)
  - Chao, Cheng-shou (Folder 6)
  - Chao, Chi (Folder 7)
  - Chao, Chih-cheng (Folder 8)
  - Chao, Chi-kang (Folder 9)
  - Chao, Hsien-cheng (Folder 10)
  - Chao, Kai (Folder 11)
  - Chao, Kuang-pei (Folder 12)
  - Chao, Kuan-tao (Folder 13)
  - Chao, Kung Abbot (Lincoln, Trebitsch) (Folder 14)
  - Chao, Kuo-hao (Folder 15)
  - Chao, Kwei-chang (Folder 16)
  - Chao, Ling-po (Folder 17)
  - Chao, Liu-fang (Folder 18)
  - Chao, Madame (Folder 19)
  - Chao, Pei-lien (Folder 20)
  - Chao, Peng-ti (Folder 21)
  - Chao, She-kuang (Folder 22)
  - Chao, Shih-lin (Folder 23)
  - Chao, Shou-shan (Folder 24)
  - Chao, Shu-i (Folder 25)
  - Chao, Shu-jung (Folder 26)
  - Chao, Tai-wen (Folder 27)
  - Chao, Te-hsing (Folder 28)
  - Chao, Teng-yu (Folder 29)
  - Chao, Thomas (Folder 30)
  - Chao, Tsu-kang (Folder 31)
  - Chao, Yuan-jen (Folder 32)
  - Chao, Yu-sung (Folder 33)
  - Charat, Luang Aduldet (Folder 34)
  - Chau, Wing-ting (Folder 35)
  - Chen Brothers (Folder 36)
  - Chen, Buddy (Folder 37)
  - Chen, Chang-chieh (Folder 38)
  - Chen, Chang-hao (Folder 39)
  - Chen, Chi-tang (Folder 40)
  - Chen, Chang-tzu (Folder 41)
  - Chen, Chao-ying (Folder 42)
  - Chen, Cheng (Folder 43)
  - Chen, Chia-mou (Folder 44)
  - Chen, Chi-cheng (Folder 45)
  - Chen, Chi-chih (Folder 46)
  - Chen, Chieh (Folder 47)
  - Chen, Chih-mai (Folder 48)
  - Chen, Chih-shuo (Folder 49)
  - Chen, Chi-hsuan (Folder 50)
  - Chen, Chi-liang (Folder 51)
  - Chen, Ching (Folder 52)
  - Chen, Ching-yun (Folder 53)
  - Chen, Chin-tao (Folder 54)
  - Chen, Chi-tang (Folder 55)
  - Chen, Chi-tien (Folder 56)
  - Chen, Chi-tsai (Folder 57)
  - Chen, Cho (Folder 58)
  - Chen, Chueh-sheng (Folder 59)
  - Chen, Chun (Folder 60)
  - Chen, Chun-chung (Folder 61)
  - Chen, Chung-fu (Folder 62)
  - Chen, Chun-hui (Folder 63)
  - Chen, Chun-pu (Folder 64)
  - Chen, En-wei (Folder 65)
  - Chen, Han-po (Folder 66)
  - Chen, Hsi-lien (Folder 67)
  - Chen, Hsing-ya (Folder 68)
  - Chen, Hsiung (Folder 69)
  - Chen, Hsun-yung (Folder 70)
  - Chen, Hui-te (Folder 71)
  - Chen, John (Folder 72)
  - Chen, Jui-tien (Folder 73)
  - Chen, Jung-chun (Folder 74)
  - Chen, K. P. (Folder 75)
  - Chen, Ken (Folder 76)
  - Chen, Ki-lap (Folder 77)
  - Chen, Kuei-ting (Folder 78)
  - Chen, Kung-po (Folder 79)
  - Chen, Kuo-fu (Folder 80)
  - Chen, Kuo-tung (Folder 81)
  - Chen, L. C. (Folder 82)
  - Chen, Liang-fu (Folder 83)
  - Chen, Liang-yu (Folder 84)
  - Chen, Lien-po (Folder 85)
  - Chen, Li-fu (Folder 86)
  - Chen, Lu (Folder 87)
  - Chen, Ming-shu (Folder 88)
  - Chen, Pei (Folder 89)
  - Chen, Pei-kun (Folder 90)
  - Chen, Peng (Folder 91)
  - Chen, Pi-chun (Folder 92)
  - Chen, Ping-chang (Folder 93)
  - Chen, Po-tao (Folder 94)
  - Chen, Pu-lei (Folder 95)
  - Chen, S. S. (Folder 96)
  - Chen, Sheng (Folder 97)
  - Chen, Shao-kuan (Folder 98)
  - Chen, Shao-ying (Folder 99)
  - Chen, Shao-yu (Folder 100)
  - Chen, Shih-hsiang (Folder 101)
  - Chen, Shih-tsai (Folder 102)
  - Chen, Shu-jen (Folder 103)
  - Chen, Shu Tan (Folder 104)
  - Chen, Shu-tung (Folder 105)
  - Chen, Ta-chi (Folder 106)
  - Chen, Ta-ching (Folder 107)
  - Chen, Ta-chun (Folder 108)
  - Chen, Tiao-yuan (Folder 109)
  - Chen, Tieh (Folder 110)
  - Chen, Tsai-li (Folder 111)
  - Chen, Tsan-po (Folder 112)
  - Chen, Tse (Folder 113)
  - Chen, Tse-min (Folder 114)
  - Chen, Tzu-hua (Folder 115)
  - Chen, Wan-jen (Folder 116)
  - Chen, Wei-yuan (Folder 117)
  - Chen, Wen-chi (Folder 118)
  - Chen, Yao-tsu (Folder 119)
  - Chen, Yi (Folder 120)
  - Chen, Yi-chen (Folder 121)
  - Chen, Yin-fei (Folder 122)
  - Chen, Yu-chih (Folder 123)
  - Chen, Yu-jen (Folder 124)
  - Chen, Yun-wen (Folder 125)
  - Chen, Yung-sheng (Folder 126)
  - Cheng, C. (Folder 127)
  - Cheng, C. H. (Folder 128)
  - Cheng, C. L. (Folder 129)
  - Cheng, Chen (Folder 130)
  - Cheng, Chao-chi (Folder 131)
  - Cheng, Chao-ching (Folder 132)
  - Cheng, Chia-chun (Folder 133)
  - Cheng, Chieh-min (Folder 134)
  - Cheng, Chien (Folder 135)
  - Cheng, Chi-lu (Folder 136)
  - Cheng, Fang-wu (Folder 137)
  - Cheng, Haugh Suey (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Cheng, Helen (Folder 2)
  - Cheng, Heng (Folder 3)
  - Cheng, Hung-nien (Folder 4)
  - Cheng, I-ming (Folder 5)
  - Cheng, K. L. (Folder 6)
  - Cheng, Ke (Folder 7)
  - Cheng, Kuan-hsun (Folder 8)
  - Cheng, Lai (Folder 9)
  - Cheng, Lieh (Folder 10)
  - Cheng, Mr. (Folder 11)
  - Cheng, Pao-nan (Folder 12)
  - Cheng, S. J. (Folder 13)
  - Cheng, Sai-hoi (Folder 14)
  - Cheng, Shao-chiung (Folder 15)
  - Cheng, She-wo (Folder 16)
  - Cheng, Shih-chun (Folder 17)
  - Cheng, Stephen (Folder 18)
  - Cheng, Tao (Folder 19)
  - Cheng, Tien-fang (Folder 20)
  - Cheng, Tien-ku (Folder 21)
  - Cheng, Wan-chun (Folder 22)
  - Chennault, Claire Lee (Folder 23)
  - Chi, C. T. (Folder 24)
  - Chi, Chun-feng (Folder 25)
  - Chi, Hsieh-yuan (Folder 26)
  - Chi, Kuo-cheng (Folder 27)
  - Chi, Kuo-fang (Folder 28)
  - Chi, Wen-ping (Folder 29)
  - Chi, Yen-ju (Folder 30)
  - Chia, Te-yueh (Folder 31)
  - Chiang, Chao-chung (Folder 32)
  - Chiang, Chi (Folder 33)
  - Chiang, Chin-shu (Folder 34)
  - Chiang, Ch'ing-kuo (Folder 35)
  - Chiang, En-chih (Folder 36)
  - Chiang, Hu (Folder 37)
  - Chiang, Hung-tang (Folder 38)
  - Chiang, Joseph (Folder 39)
  - Chiang, Kai-shek (Folder 40)
  - Chiang, Kang-hu (Folder 41)
  - Chiang, Kuang-nai (Folder 42)
  - Chiang, Lu-chien (Folder 43)
  - Chiang, Meng-lin (Folder 44)
  - Chiang, Monlin (Folder 45)
  - Chiang, Po-cheng (Folder 46)
  - Chiang, Poli (Folder 47)
  - Chiang, Shao-chieh (Folder 48)
  - Chiang, Shiao Dawn (Folder 49)
  - Chiang, Ting-fu (Folder 50)
  - Chiang, Ting-wen (Folder 51)
  - Chiang, Tsan-po (Folder 52)
  - Chiang, Tso-pin (Folder 53)
  - Chiang, Tsun-wei (Folder 54)
  - Chiang, Wei-kuo (Folder 55)
  - Chiang, Yen-chung (Folder 56)
  - Chiang, Yuh-foo (Folder 57)
  - Chiao, Ying (Folder 58)
  - Chie, Paik San (Folder 59)
  - Chien, Ai-tsu (Folder 60)
  - Chien, C. T. (Folder 61)
  - Chien, Chang-chao (Folder 62)
  - Chien, Chia-chi (Folder 63)
  - Chien, Hsueh-sen (Folder 64)
  - Chien, Jui-sun (Folder 65)
  - Chien, Ta-chun (Folder 66)
  - Chien, Ta-huai (Folder 67)
  - Chien, Tai (Folder 68)
  - Chien, Tien-ho (Folder 69)
  - Chien, Tso-lun (Folder 70)
  - Chien, Tuan-sheng (Folder 71)
  - Chien, Tung-liang (Folder 72)
  - Chien, Ying (Folder 73)
  - Chih, Feng-cheng (Folder 74)
  - Chin, Chang (Folder 75)
  - Chin, Fen (Folder 76)
  - Chin, Hsien-chang (Folder 77)
  - Chin, Hua (Folder 78)
  - Chin, Jung-kuei (Folder 79)
  - Chin, Lung-te (Folder 80)
  - Chin, Pang-hsien (Folder 81)
  - Chin, Pao-tung (Folder 82)
  - Chin, Shao-wei (Folder 83)
  - Chin, Tai-feng (Folder 84)
  - Chin, Tang-hsien (Folder 85)
  - Chin, Te-chun (Folder 86)
  - Chin, Tseng-cheng (Folder 87)
  - Chin, Yung-kwei (Folder 88)
  - China
    - Pre-, 1949 (Folder 89)
    - Post-, 1949
      - General (Folder 90)
      - American funds and property (Folder 91)
      - Banking regulations (Folder 92)
      - Foreign nationals (Folder 93)
      - Law (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Private enterprise (Folder 2)
  - China Student Interpreter Corps (Folder 3)
  - China Trade Act Companies (Folder 4)
  - Ching, Nien Tuan (Folder 5)
  - Chino, Franklin (Folder 6)
  - Chisholm, Robert D. (Folder 7)
  - Chiu, Chang-wei (Folder 8)
  - Chot'epachapu (Folder 9)
  - Chou, Chen-lin (Folder 10)
  - Chou, Chih-jou (Folder 11)
  - Chou, Chi-kang (Folder 12)
  - Chou, Chung-liang (Folder 13)
  - Chou, Chung-yueh (Folder 14)
  - Chou, En-lai (Folder 15)
  - Chou, Fa-yen (Folder 16)
  - Chou, Fu-cheng (Folder 17)
  - Chou, Fu-hai (Folder 18)
  - Chou, Hsi-meng (Folder 19)
  - Chou, Hsueh-chang (Folder 20)
  - Chou, Hun-jen (Folder 21)
  - Chou, Hun-yuan (Folder 22)
  - Chou, K. J. (Folder 23)
  - Chou, Kang-shen (Folder 24)
  - Chou, Kuo-chiang (Folder 25)
  - Chou, Li-sheng (Folder 26)
  - Chou, Lung-hsiang (Folder 27)
  - Chou, Lung-kuang (Folder 28)
  - Chou, Ping-lin (Folder 29)
  - Chou, Shou-chen (Folder 31)
  - Chou, Shou-lan (Folder 32)
  - Chou, Sung-sheng (Folder 33)
  - Chou, Tai (Folder 34)
  - Chou, Ti-ping (Folder 35)
  - Chou, Tso-min (Folder 36)
  - Chou, Tsu-kwang (Folder 37)
  - Chou, Tzu-an (Folder 38)
  - Chou, Wei-kang (Folder 39)
  - Chou, Wen-lung (Folder 40)
  - Chou, Yah-wei (Folder 41)
  - Chou, Yi-chun (Folder 42)
  - Chou, Ying-tsung (Folder 43)
  - Chow, Albert (Folder 44)
  - Chow, Chih-jou (Folder 45)
  - Chow, Chin-jao (Folder 46)
  - Chow, Chou-son (Folder 47)
  - Chow, David W. (Folder 48)
  - Chow, S. K. (Folder 49)
  - Chow, Wen Tsing (Folder 50)
  - Christiansen, H. F. (Folder 51)
  - Chu, Chang-keng (Folder 52)
  - Chu, Cheng (Folder 53)
  - Chu, Chia-hua (Folder 54)
  - Chu, Ching-lai (Folder 55)
  - Chu, Chuan-yuan (Folder 56)
  - Chu, Chun-chia (Folder 57)
  - Chu, George (Folder 58)
  - Chu, Hsin-cheng (Folder 59)
  - Chu, Hsin-ming (Folder 60)
  - Chu, Hsueh-fan (Folder 61)
  - Chu, Hui-jih (Folder 62)
  - Chu, I-chieh (Folder 63)
  - Chu, J. T. (Folder 64)
  - Chu, Kuo-hong (Folder 65)
  - Chu, Li-ho (Folder 66)
  - Chu, Lynn (Folder 67)
  - Chu, Min-yi (Folder 68)
  - Chu, Pei-te (Folder 69)
  - Chu, Shao-chou (Folder 70)
  - Chu, Shao-liang (Folder 71)
  - Chu, Shen (Folder 72)
  - Chu, Shih-ming (Folder 73)
  - Chu, Shou-kuang (Folder 74)
  - Chu, Teh (Folder 75)
  - Chu, Ting-chi (Folder 76)
  - Chu, Tu-hsing (Folder 77)
  - Chu, Wei-tsung (Folder 78)
  - Chu, Wen-piao (Folder 79)
  - Chu, Y. P. (Folder 80)
  - Chu, Yu-tsang (Folder 81)
  - Chui, Kwang-hsiu (Folder 82)
  - Chung, Hsun-jen (Folder 83)
  - Chung, Margaret (Folder 84)
  - Chung, Wing-kwong (Folder 85)
  - Chwang, David (Folder 86)
  - Cisneros, Garrido (Folder 87)
  - Clark, Punjaub (Folder 88)
  - Clarke, Hilda (Folder 89)
  - Clubb, Oliver Edmund (Folder 90)
  - Coca-Cola (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cohen, Morris A. (Folder 2)
  - Colton, Wendell (Folder 3)
  - Cooper, Morris (Folder 4)
  - Corrit, Aage (Folder 5)
  - Cosme, Henri (Folder 6)
  - Co Tui, Dr. (Folder 7)
  - Co Tui, Frank (Folder 8)
  - Coughlin, Father (Folder 9)
  - Coughlin, Ray (Folder 10)
  - Coutain, Pierre (Folder 11)
  - Cubria, Octavio (Folder 12)
  - Cullens, James (Folder 13)
  - Cunard White Star Limited (Folder 14)
  - Currie, Lauchlin (Folder 15)
  - Cushing, William (Folder 16)
  - Dang, Donald (Folder 17)
  - Davis, Tom (Folder 18)
  - Davis, Lowell (Folder 19)
  - Day, Mrs. Kenneth (Folder 20)
  - Dean, Vera M. (Folder 21)
  - Deane, Samuel (Folder 22)
  - Deane, T. Y. (Folder 23)
  - DeCoux, Vice Admiral (Folder 24)
  - De Clerk, Father (Folder 25)
  - Dehmelt, Kapitan (Folder 26)
  - De Jaegher, Raymond (Folder 27)
  - De Lange, Captain (Folder 28)
  - Dellin, Louis A. (Folder 29)
  - Dennen, Leon (Folder 30)
  - Dennett, Prescott (Folder 31)
  - Dennys, Lancelot (Folder 32)
  - De Stael, Rene (Folder 33)
  - Devals, Adriang (Folder 34)
  - Dibabha, Aditya (Folder 35)
  - Diesch, Franz (Folder 36)
  - Dolan, James S. (Folder 37)
  - Domondon, Sixto (Folder 38)
  - Donovan, William J. (Folder 39)
  - Dotzauer, Mr. (Folder 40)
  - Douglas, Baron Van Breugel (Folder 41)
  - Douglas, Fred T. (Folder 42)
  - Douglas, William O. (Folder 43)
  - Dschou, T. S. (Folder 44)
  - Du Berrier, Hilaire (Folder 45)
  - Dubois, W. E. (Folder 46)
  - Duggleby, A. F. (Folder 47)
  - Dunlap, A. M. (Folder 48)
  - Dunsing, W. (Folder 49)
  - DuVal, Miles P. (Folder 50)
  - Dzau, Linson (Folder 51)
  - East Asiatic Company (Folder 52)
  - Eastlake, Roland (Folder 53)
  - Eckelmann, Gerald (Folder 54)
  - Edmonds, James E. (Folder 55)
  - Eggleston, Frederick (Folder 56)
  - Eh-lu-chin-pa-tuh (Folder 57)
  - E-le-chun (Folder 58)
  - El Huseini, Amin (Folder 59)
  - Elliott, Victor S. (Folder 60)
  - Empis, Carlos (Folder 61)
  - En-ke-pa-tu (Folder 62)
  - Erben, H. F. (Folder 63)
  - Escarra, Jean (Folder 64)
  - Eschig, W. (Folder 65)
  - Eschler, Josef (Folder 66)
  - Essoyan, Roy (Folder 67)
  - Evans, W. A. (Folder 68)
  - Falkenhausen, Alexander (Folder 69)
  - Fan, Chang-chiang (Folder 70)
  - Fan, Chu-hsien (Folder 71)
  - Fan, Chung-yun (Folder 72)
  - Fan, Han-chieh (Folder 73)
  - Fan, Shao-tseng (Folder 74)
  - Fan, Sung-pu (Folder 75)
  - Fan, Tze-ying (Folder 76)
  - Fang, Chen-wu (Folder 77)
  - Fang, Hing-ting (Folder 78)
  - Fang, Pen-jen (Folder 79)
  - Fang, Sheng-heng (Folder 80)
  - Fang, Sung-fu (Folder 81)
  - Fang, Ting-ying (Folder 82)
  - Fang, Tsung-ao (Folder 83)
  - Farhney, Merry (Folder 84)
  - Fei, Tsu-yi (Folder 85)
  - Felton, Monica (Folder 86)
  - Fen, Ko-yuan (Folder 87)
  - Fen, Su-chih (Folder 88)
  - Feng, An-pang (Folder 89)
  - Feng, C. T. (Folder 90)
  - Feng, Chan-hai (Folder 91)
  - Feng, Chih-an (Folder 92)
  - Feng, Chin-tsai (Folder 93)
  - Feng, Han-ching (Folder 94)
  - Feng, Ping-shun (Folder 95)
  - Feng, Pin-tai (Folder 96)
  - Feng, Sheng-fa (Folder 97)
  - Feng, Yu-hsiang (Folder 98)
  - Field, Frederick V. (Folder 99)
  - Fischbacher, Jacques (Folder 100)
  - Fischer, Dr. (Folder 101)
  - Fischer, Oscar (Folder 102)
  - Fistere, J. (Folder 103)
  - Fletcher, Mr. (Folder 104)
  - Flowers, W. S. (Folder 105)
  - Foin, Victor (Folder 106)
  - Fong, Ben W. (Folder 107)
  - Fong, T. Y. (Folder 108)
  - Forkner, Claude (Folder 109)
  - Forman, Harrison (Folder 110)
  - Formosa (Taiwan), Mutual Security Program, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Forms (Folder 2)
  - Forster, Charles (Folder 3)
  - Franklin, C. S. (Folder 4)
  - Franklin, Cornel (Folder 5)
  - Fu, Chung-fang (Folder 6)
  - Fu, Ping-chang (Folder 7)
  - Fu, Shih-shuo (Folder 8)
  - Fu, Siao-en (Folder 9)
  - Fu, Tsun (Folder 10)
  - Fu, Tso-i (Folder 11)
  - Fu, Wong-chen (Folder 12)
  - Fuchs, Walter (Folder 13)
  - Fulbright, James W. (Folder 14)
  - Fung, Yee-fong (Folder 15)
  - Gan, I. (Folder 16)
  - Gande, Bill (Folder 17)
  - Gardiner, William H. (Folder 18)
  - Gauss, Clarence (Folder 19)
  - Gearhart (Folder 20)
  - Gelferish, Emil (Folder 21)
  - General Commodities Corporation, Ltd. (Folder 22)
  - Gerli, Quirino (Folder 23)
  - German Embassy personnel, Tokyo, 1943 (Folder 24)
  - Gilleland, R. E. (Folder 25)
  - Gilley, Evelyn (Folder 26)
  - Glathe, Alfred (Folder 27)
  - Glesinger, Paul (Folder 28)
  - Gloohoff, George (Folder 29)
  - Gomersall, William (Folder 30)
  - Gorge, Mr. (Folder 31)
  - Gorman, George (Folder 32)
  - Gorman, Niel A. (Folder 33)
  - Gould, Randall (Folder 34)
  - Gowen, Herbert (Folder 35)
  - Grajdanzev, Andrew (Folder 36)
  - Gray, Adeline (Folder 37)
  - Grayburn, Vanderlur (Folder 38)
  - Gregersen, Magnus (Folder 39)
  - Grimsdale, General (Folder 40)
  - Grinnell, Carroll (Folder 41)
  - Griswold, Glenn (Folder 42)
  - Grott, M. (Folder 43)
  - Guillermaz, Jacques (Folder 44)
  - Gundelfinger, F. D. (Folder 45)
  - Hass & Schreiner (Folder 46)
  - Haber, Otto (Folder 47)
  - Hackett, Bessie (Folder 48)
  - Hahn, Emily (Folder 49)
  - Hall, Adelia (Folder 50)
  - Han, Ching-wei (Folder 51)
  - Han, Dr. (Folder 52)
  - Han, Fu-chu (Folder 53)
  - Han, H. C. T. (Folder 54)
  - Han, Li Wu (Folder 55)
  - Han, Te-chin (Folder 56)
  - Han, To-feng (Folder 57)
  - Han, Yuan-chieh (Folder 58)
  - Hang, Li-wu (Folder 59)
  - Hanning, Captain (Folder 60)
  - Hansen, Jens H. (Folder 61)
  - Hao, Tsu-chu (Folder 62)
  - Hapenbrack, G. M. (Folder 63)
  - Hardoon, Ezra (Hardoon, Silas, estate of) (Folder 64)
  - Harkson, U. S. (Folder 65)
  - Harrell, Judson G. (Folder 66)
  - Harzdorf, Baron (Folder 67)
  - Hata, Shunroku (Folder 68)
  - Hauser, Ernest (Folder 69)
  - Haushofer, Karl (Folder 70)
  - Hausmann, Schultz (Folder 71)
  - Haven, Dwight E. (Folder 72)
  - Hayakashi, Kitaro (Folder 73)
  - Hayashi, Senjuro (Folder 74)
  - Hayes, John D. (Folder 75)
  - Healey, Thomas (Folder 76)
  - Heesch, Henry (Folder 77)
  - Henkel, Louis (Folder 78)
  - Henningsen, A. B. (Folder 79)
  - Hepfield, John (Folder 80)
  - Hinton, Joan Chase (Folder 81)
  - Hinton, William (Folder 82)
  - Hiranuma, Baron (Folder 83)
  - Hiranuma, Kiichiro (Folder 84)
  - Hirata, Isao (Folder 85)
  - Hirota, Koki (Folder 86)
  - Hishihari, Takashi (Folder 87)
  - Ho, Chang-kung (Folder 88)
  - Ho, Cheng-chun (Folder 89)
  - Ho, Cheng-pu (Folder 90)
  - Ho, Chien (Folder 91)
  - Ho, Chi-kung (Folder 92)
  - Ho, Chi-li (Folder 93)
  - Ho, Chin-nien (Folder 94)
  - Ho, Chu-fei (Folder 95)
  - Ho, Chu-kuo (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Ho, Feng-lin (Folder 2)
  - Ho, Feng-shan (Folder 3)
  - Ho, Hsiang-ning (Folder 4)
  - Ho, Kuo-kuang (Folder 5)
  - Ho, Lien (Folder 6)
  - Ho, Lung (Folder 7)
  - Ho, Mow Lan (Folder 8)
  - Ho, P. H. (Folder 9)
  - Ho, Pei-yung (Folder 10)
  - Ho, Pin-tsuan (Folder 11)
  - Ho, Ping-lin (Folder 12)
  - Ho, Robert (Folder 13)
  - Ho, Sui (Folder 14)
  - Ho, Ting-liu (Folder 15)
  - Ho, Tzu-chien (Folder 16)
  - Ho, Yao-tsu (Folder 17)
  - Ho, Yin (Folder 18)
  - Ho, Ying-chin (Folder 10)
  - Ho, Yun-kuei (Folder 20)
  - Hoebich, Mr. (Folder 21)
  - Hoffman, Paul, "Communism and What It Will Do to You,", 1952 (Folder 22)
  - Hofmier (Folder 23)
  - Holland, A. E. (Folder 24)
  - Holsser, Henry (Folder 25)
  - Homma, Masaharu (Folder 26)
  - Hoo, Hsien-chung (Folder 27)
  - Hoo, Victor (Folder 28)
  - Hoover Commission (Folder 29)
  - Hoover, Lyman (Folder 30)
  - Horr, Ralph (Folder 31)
  - Hoshino, Naoki (Folder 32)
  - Hou, Kwei-chang (Folder 33)
  - Hou, T. P. (Folder 34)
  - Houston, Herbert (Folder 35)
  - Howard, Harry (Folder 36)
  - Howard, Jack (Folder 37)
  - Howes, James M. (Folder 38)
  - Hsi, Chia (Folder 39)
  - Hsi, En-sui (Folder 40)
  - Hsi, Te-mou (Folder 41)
  - Hsia, Chi-feng (Folder 42)
  - Hsia, Chin (Folder 43)
  - Hsia, Chin-lin (Folder 44)
  - Hsia, Chu-chung (Folder 45)
  - Hsia, J. C. (Folder 46)
  - Hsia, P. F. (Folder 47)
  - Hsia, Peng (Folder 48)
  - Hsia, Tou-yin (Folder 49)
  - Hsia, Wei (Folder 50)
  - Hsia, Yu (Folder 51)
  - Hsiang, Chin-chuan (Folder 52)